(Leonard:)I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
See, Penny is my fiancée.
(Man:)Really?
(Man:)I've never seen her wear
an engagement ring.
WOLOWITZ AND KOOTHRAPPALI:
Really?
(Man:)So, am I to presume
(Man:)that her flirtation was
just a sales technique?
(Leonard:)I think so.
(Man:)When will I learn?
(Man:)It's just like the cute girl
at the pet store all over again.
(Leonard:)Excuse me?
(Man:)Oh, uh, she touched my arm
for five Mississippis,
(Man:)and I bought
a $2,000 iguana habitat.
(Man:)Which she was always too busy
to come over and see.
(Man:)You give these to Penny.
You're, you're a lucky man.
(Man with Flowers:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)Sorry.
(Man:)Oh, uh...
(Man:)You probably don't want her
to see this.